This is a 3D visualization of a Ulam spiral (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ulam_spiral).
In this file, all prime numbers (and the number 1) are represented by solid cubes, while composite numbers are hollow cubes.
the numbers range from 1 to 225. 
The numbers are read by moving along the positive X direction, the negative Y direction, and the negative Z direction.
For the sake of visual clarity 1 is represented as prime.
To find the top 'plate' of this spiral, look for the only 3 consecutive solid cubes.
The figure below represents the top 'plate' view the object left to right, top to bottom, top plate to bottom plate. 

■ ■ ■ □ ■
□ ■ □ □ □
■ □ ■ □ □
□ ■ □ ■ □
□ □ ■ □ □

Dropbox link to STL:
https://www.dropbox.com/sh/h3ujhz4oerf6j09/AAAMe6DmHMf3iYz_p-MMglQCa?dl=0